Guide to the Walter Thabit papers, 1950-2004
Thabit, Walter papers, 1950-2004
- Series III. Planning Projects
  - Cooper Square (CS)
    - Community Board 3 Task Force - Astor place (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Cooper Square, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Homeless Coalition – New York City (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - New York Preservation Archive Project (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Fifth Avenue Committee (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - 14th Street Rezoning II (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - The Enterprise Foundation (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Blaustein/Rutgers/Hughes (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Lowdown (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - C.S. Steering, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Cooper Square, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Cooper Square, 1990 – 1991 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Cooper Square, 1992 – 1993 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Cooper Square, 1994 –1995 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Cooper Square, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Cooper Square, 1996 – (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Cooper Square/LES, 1998-2000 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Cooper Square, 1998-2000 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Cooper Square Retreat, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Cooper Square, 2001-2004 (Box 65, Folder 22)
      Includes 2004 Cooper Square Committee 45th Anniversary Gala booklet with a history of committee
    - Cooper Square - Progress and Reports (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - 8th Street Rezoning (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Small Projects (SP)
    - SP-1: White Plains - Surveys, Interviews (Box 39, Folder 7)
      A housing plan for a Community Action Program in White Plains
    - SP-2: White Plains - Programming (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - SP-3: White Plains - Reports (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - SP-4: World Trade Center I (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Major fight against the Rockefeller project
    - SP-5: World Trade Center Speech (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - SP-6: World Trade Center II (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - SP-7: Vacant Land - Information (Box 39, Folder 13)
      Documentation of the existence of small site on which housing could be built instead of city's massive displacement projects. Consulted to the Metropolitan Council on Housing.
    - SP-8: Columbia Area Redevelopment Comm. (Box 39, Folder 14)
      Advocacy planning for waterfront community threatened by Port Authority expansion
    - SP-9: Park Slope Rehabilitation Effort (Box 39, Folder 15)
      Short lived group that was overtaken.
    - SP-10: Welfare Island Proposal (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Opposition to housing development on the Island
    - SP-11: Southwest Bronx (Box 39, Folder 17)
      Proposed Program
    - SP-12: Newburgh - Report Draft (Box 39, Folder 18)
      Preparation of marketing flyer for an industrial site
    - SP-13: Secaucus (Box 39, Folder 19)
      Testifying for the Council
    - SP-14: Stamford Zoning Case - Smithfield Pt. (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - SP-15: Glen Island Estates (Box 39, Folder 21)
      Resort development proposal
    - SP-16: Lynch I (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - SP-17: Lynch II (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - SP-18: Broome St. Expressway (Box 39, Folder 24)
      A big struggle to defeat the Moses proposed lower Manhattan Expressway
    - SP-19: Broome St. Expressway II (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - SP-20: North Jersey Housing Analysis, 1960's (Box 39, Folder 26)
      An analysis of the housing market
    - SP-21: Jersey City Mapping (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - SP-22: Caven Point - Waterfront (Box 39, Folder 28)
      What to do with a soon to be released U.S. Army Terminal
    - SP-23: Caven Point - Eco. Base. (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - SP-24: TRW Towing (Box 40, Folder 6)
      A vigorous fight against a towing operation
    - SP-25: Arts Center (Box 40, Folder 7)
      Arts Center proposal for the site of the Greenwich Village jail, prepared for Koch's campaign against Carmine DeSapio
    - SP-26: Cabarets (Box 40, Folder 8)
      Rules and regulations governing cabarets, related to 8th street rezoning fight. (Next folder)
    - SP-27: 8th St. Rezoning (Box 40, Folder 9)
      Defeat of an attempt to zone cabarets out of 8th Street in Greenwich Village
    - SP-28: ALPA Community Reports (Box 40, Folder 10)
      An attempt to make professional planning available to local communities
    - SP-29: ALPA Interviews (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - SP-30: MFY - Housing Gap Report (Box 40, Folder 12)
      Mobilization For Youth, housing need on the Lower East Side.
    - SP-31: MFY - Administrative & Other (Box 40, Folder 13)
      Mostly Mobilization for Youth (MFY)'s Housing Clinic of which Thabit was a Director for at some point.
    - SP-32: Stage West - Programming (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - SP-33: Stage West - Marketing/Costs (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - SP-34: Stage West - Background - 1933, 1933 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - SP-35: Police Headquarters (Box 40, Folder 17)
      Developing a proposal to convert an old Police Headquarters building to luxury residential use. Costs were too high.
    - SP-36: Renaissance 42 - Background, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      Development of a sales brochure for a piece of 42nd Street property
    - SP-37: Renaissance 42 - Housing Market Background 1987, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - SP-38: Renaissance - Design Background (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - SP-39: Renaissance 42 - Original Drafts (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - SP-40: Renaissance 42 - 3rd Draft (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - SP-41: Al-Fouzan Background (Box 43, Folder 29)
      Develoment proposal for a site on the Costa del Sol.
    - SP-42: Fousan Al Fouzan (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - SP-43: Fort Hamilton - Preliminary Reports (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Motel and residential prospects for family property
    - SP-44: Ft. Hamilton Motel - Current Work (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - SP-45: Thabit Site (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - SP-46: Materials & Services - Ft. Hamilton (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - SP-47: Boorady - Dunkirk (Box 44, Folder 5)
      A look at an urban renewal site for a brother-in-law
    - SP-48: Hamptonburg - Background (Box 44, Folder 6)
      Subdivision possibility in upstate NY, for Thabit's brother Bob's client.
    - SP-49: Hamptonburg (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Series IV. Department of Transportation
  - Ferries (DO-F)
    - Ferries Planning
      - DO-F1: Ferry Planning - Programming (Box 7, Folder 31)
        Materials related to the developing of the work program
      - DO-F2: Subregional Report FY 1985/1986/1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
        Quarterly reports to UMTA (Metropolitan Transportation Authority) describing program
      - DO-F3: Ferry Vehicle Survey (Box 7, Folder 33)
        A survey of vehicle drivers taking the ferry from Staten Island (SI) to Manhattan
      - DO-F4: Staten Island Ferry Ridership (Box 7, Folder 34)
        Analysis of commuting to Manhattan by mode
      - DO-F5: History- Ferries (Box 7, Folder 35)
        Book exerpt
      - DO-F6: SI (Staten Island) Trolley Museum (Box 7, Folder 36)
        Proposed Trolley line and museum
      - DO-F7: Transit - SI Ferry Flash Pass (Box 7, Folder 37)
        Idea for facilitating multi-modal ferry trips
      - DO-F8: Ferry Ads (Box 7, Folder 38)
        Proposals for putting ads into the Staten Island papers to increase ridership
      - DO-F9: Staten Island Ferry Improvement (Box 7, Folder 39)
        Various proposals for improving system and fare increases
      - DO-F10: Ferries - SIRT (Staten Island Rapid Transit) Planning (Box 7, Folder 40)
        Study of Staten Island rapid transit
      - DO-F11: DOT North Shore Study (Box 7, Folder 41)
        Study of abandoned SIRT line as possible transit link to ferry
      - DO-F12: Rikers Island (Box 7, Folder 42)
        City's interest in providing ferry service to Rikers Island
      - DO-F13: DOT 69th Street Ferry Proposal (Box 7, Folder 43)
        Proposal for a new municipal ferry service in an attempt to use two new small ferry boats more.
      - DO-F14: Bay Parkway Proposal (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - DO-F15: 39th Street Proposal (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - South Ferry Plaza
      - DO-F16: Ferry Terminal Studies (Box 7, Folder 46)
        Efforts to improve the pedestrian crossing and enlarge plaza prior to South Ferry Plaza development was initiated. Other terminals.
      - DO-F17: South Ferry Plaza- RFP (Box 7, Folder 47)
        Selected portions of the RFP for development of the site.
      - DO-F18: South Ferry Plaza - Transportation Briefing (Box 7, Folder 48)
        Presentations of transportation issues by developers.
      - DO-F19: South Ferry Plaza- Transportation (Box 7, Folder 49)
        Evaluation of proposals by PDC staff and consultants and by DOT staff.
    - CEQR- City Environmental Quality Review
      - DO-F20: Harbor Commuter - CEQR: (Box 7, Folder 50)
        The first ferry service to seek a 5 year permit; its correspondence with CEQR staff.
      - DO-F21: CEQR- Executive Order #91 (Box 7, Folder 51)
        City's rules and regulations
      - DO-F22: PITC (Dept. of Ports, International Trade and Commerce) CEQR (Box 7, Folder 52)
        The Department of Ports, International Trade and Commerce was pursuing a CEQR for the use of Pier 17.
      - DO-F23: Board of Estimate Forms (Box 7, Folder 53)
        Start of putting together a recommendation to the Board of Estimate
      - DO-F24: Board of Estimate Submission (Box 7, Folder 54)
        Gradual development of submission
    - Section 8 Grant Proposals
      - DO-F25: Section 8 Study Proposals (Box 7, Folder 55)
        Early initial proposals which never even got out of our Bureau
      - DO-F26: Section 8 Project Proposals (Box 7, Folder 56)
        Proposal to improve Staten Island Ferry ridership
      - DO-F27: UMTA Section 8 Grant Proposal (Box 7, Folder 57)
        This and the following three files contain the long period of processing a New York Ferries Development Program- Never funded
      - DO-F28: Section 8 Work Program- Ferries (Box 7, Folder 58)
        The long period of processing a New York Ferries Development Program- Never funded
      - DO-F29: UMTA Section 8 Study Proposal (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - DO-F30: UMTA Section 8 Grant Proposal, Final and Rejected (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Section 8 Program Proposals, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Section 8 UMTA - Revised Work Program (Box 63, Folder 8 A)
    - Administrative/Programming
      - DO-F31: Time Sheets, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 61)
        Some information about filling out time cards
      - DO-F32: White Meeting Agendas (Box 7, Folder 62)
        Notes for my meetings with Commissioner White
      - DO-F33: New York Ferries Development Consultants (Box 7, Folder 63)
        Consultants interested in supplying Walter Thabit and associates with services
      - DO-F34: Telephone Numbers (Box 7, Folder 64)
        Mailing list, T of O
      - DO-F35: Ferry Planning Budget (Box 7, Folder 65)
        Proposed budget, never approved by OMB.
      - DO-F36: Programming New Ferries (Box 7, Folder 66)
        Unusual Issues
      - DO-F37: Miscellaneous Ferry (Box 7, Folder 67)
        Miscellaneous material including examples of letterhead.
      - Staten Island Ferry Transit Flash-pass (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Staten Island Terminal Improvements (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Staten Island Ferry Programming (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Staten Island Ferry Riders (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Ferry By Vehicle - Survey (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - South Ferry Plaza (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Whitehall Terminal Plaza Scheme (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Ferries - Application Guide Revision (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Docking Potentials (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Permit Fees (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Ferry Planning, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - CEQR - BD. OFEST. PITC. DOT. (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - Waterborne Project (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Harbor Ferry Council (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - Port Authority Ferries (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Surveys - Evaluation (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - Ferries - Related Studies (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - Fast Ferry Papers (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - Ferry Criteria (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous - Ferry (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - Other Municipal Ferry Proposals (Box 63, Folder 25)
      - Programming - New Ferries (Box 63, Folder 26)
      - Waterborne Policy (Box 63, Folder 27)
      - Ferries, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 28)
      - Misc. Ferry Applications (Box 63, Folder 29)
      - Ferry Services, September 22, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 30)
      - Rikers Island (Box 63, Folder 32)
      - Ferry Expansion Report - Copies, September 1985 (Box 63, Folder 33)
      - Conference - Papers to Review (Box 63, Folder 34)
      - Metranet Ferry Conference, April 5, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - International Maritime Expo, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Port Authority Ferry Survey, February 1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Chelsea Piers (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Status of New Ferry Services (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Monitoring - Ferries (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Ferry Conferences (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Boston Chapter 91 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Ferry Planning (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Regency Fishing (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - 69th Street Service - Man Exp. (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Sea Line Co. Inc. - Lubowicki (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Harbor Commuter Issues (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Harbor Commuter - Bayonne/Keypt. (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Harbor Commuter - Highlands (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Harbor Commuter - Jersey City (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Harbor Commuter - Monmouth Fulton Ferry (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Harbor Commuter - Keyport (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Manhattan Express - Rockaways (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Port Liberte (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Hydrolines - Rennerts (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Tradebase - Fort Lee (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Kontaratos - Roosevelt Island (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Arcorp - Slip 5 (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Harbor Commuter - Keansborg (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - Harbor Commuter - Fulton Ferry (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - Tradebase - Elizabeth (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - Arcorp - 38th Street (Box 64, Folder 28)
      - Sloan - Laguardia (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Potential Ferry Routes and Docking Sites
      - DO-F38: Port Authority Trans-Hudson Studies (Box 7, Folder 68)
        Materials and notes on Port Authority analysis of commuter growth and the part ferries may play in transporting them.
      - DO-F39: Port Authority Hoboken Ferry (Box 7, Folder 69)
        Port Authority proposal for Hoboken/Battery Park City ferry and opposition
      - DO-F40: Hunters Point/42nd Street Ferry (Box 7, Folder 70)
        An old Port Authority for a Queens/Manhattan ferry.
      - DO-F41: Trump, Television City (Box 7, Folder 71)
        Attempts to get Trump to include ferry docking in West Side project.
      - DO-F42: Port Richmond Study (Box 7, Folder 72)
        Initial work on updating Port Authority feasibility for high speed service
      - DO-F43: RFP Piers 9, 11 & 13 (Box 7, Folder 73)
        Issues raised by lease of Piers 9 and 11 without priority for ferries
      - DO-F44: East River Landing- PDC (Box 7, Folder 74)
        Status of Pier 11 (the most heavily used dock in Manhattan) as future development site
      - DO-F45: Ferries- Docking (Box 7, Folder 75)
        Other Potentials
      - DO-F46: Roosevelt Island (Box 7, Folder 76)
        RFP for ferry services and other items
      - DO-F47: Jamaica Bay Task Force (Box 7, Folder 77)
        Interest in increasing the number of Rockaway stops
      - DO-F48: Gateway National Park Ferries (Box 7, Folder 78)
        Government interest in ferry services to Gateway
    - Coordination with other Agencies
      - DO-F49: PITC Fees (Box 7, Folder 79)
        Discussion on fees for docking with Department of Ports, International Trade and Commission
      - DO-F50: Docks and Terminals (Box 7, Folder 80)
        Map of potential docking sites with notes on use of Whitehall Terminal
      - DO-F51: DOT/PIC Coordination (Box 7, Folder 81)
        Memos and other materials relating to Department of Ports, International Trade and Commission
      - DO-F52: Landside Access (Box 7, Folder 82)
        A City Planning Department study of docking sites
      - DO-F53: PITC Ecker Opus (Box 7, Folder 83)
        A graduate student's consultant report on pricing ferry landings that DOT opposed
      - DO-F54: Zoning for ferries (Box 7, Folder 84)
        City Planning initiative to revise waterfront zoning which includes finding a use group for ferries
      - DO-F55: Pier 84 RFP (Box 7, Folder 85)
        RFP for a permanent development of Pier 84 (West Side, Midtown) which is also being used as a ferry dock.
      - PITC/DOT/DCP Coordination (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Handicapped (DH)
    - General
      - DH-1: Quarterly Reports (Box 16, Folder 17)
        Required quarterly reports that give an overall view of what the handicapped division was about- principally designing and implementing a para-transit system for the handicapped.
      - DH-2: Regulations, 504 Et Al (Box 16, Folder 18)
        Copy of federal regulations on providing equal access to the handicapped.
      - DH-3: Miscellaneous Memos (Box 16, Folder 19)
        Memos by various authors.
      - DH-4: Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - DH-5: Handicapped Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - DH-6: Advisory Committee; Technical Committee (Box 16, Folder 22)
        Minutes of these meetings and related information.
      - DH-7: Research Proposal, NCHRP (Box 16, Folder 23)
        Proposal to develop methods for measuring the cost effectiveness of various options which satisfy the needs of the handicapped.
      - DH-8: Grant Proposals (Box 16, Folder 24)
        Various proposals for studies related to transportation for the elderly and handicapped
      - DH-9: Draft Questionnaire (Box 16, Folder 25)
        For inventory transportation services provided by non-transportation agencies.
      - DH-10: Funding Source Study (Box 16, Folder 26)
        More detail on proposal for survey mentioned in DH-9
      - DH-11: Funding Source Study- Background (Box 16, Folder 27)
        More materials on funding prospects
      - Handicapped (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Handicapped Demand (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Health Area Maps (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Handicapped Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Handicapped Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Studies
      - DH-12: Census 1970/Disabled 16-64 (Box 16, Folder 28)
        Census data used in analysis
      - DH-13: Sample Census Form (Box 16, Folder 29)
        Detailed form 1 in 20 fills
      - DH-14: Boro Health Area Maps (Box 16, Folder 30)
        Maps used in analysis
      - DH-15: NHIS Data 1972 (Box 16, Folder 31)
        Results of survey of handicapped
      - DH-16: Small Area Distribution (Box 16, Folder 32)
        Distribution of handicapped by NYC Health Area
      - DH-17: Easyride Evaluation (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - DH-18: Honolulu Paratransit Case Study (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - DH-19: CBO- Urban Transit for Handicapped Persons (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - DH-20: Charac. And Transit Needs of the Handicapped, Tri-State ARI January 16, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        A Tri-State survey of the handicapped primary use in the development of the project's estimate
      - DH-21: UMTA Methods Demo. Travel Behaviour, TH. Koffman Paper- Portland (Box 17, Folder 5)
        Various publications on the Transit Handicapped
      - DH-22: Demand- Sections A & B (Box 17, Folder 6)
        Analysis of TH transportation demand
      - DH-23: Chapter II- Definition of Need (Box 17, Folder 7)
        More analysis and a report
      - DH-24: Latent Demand (Box 17, Folder 8)
        Explores the question of how much traveling would the Transit Handicapped do if they had the opportunity.
      - DH-25: Final Trip Demand Estimates (Box 17, Folder 9)
        The culmination of research efforts
      - DH-26: U.S. Census Data 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Major Study and Analysis of Surveys
      - DH-27: Handicapped Alert- Background (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - DH-28: Con Ed Analysis (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - DH-29: Handicapped Alert- 1st General Tables (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - DH-30: Handicapped Alert- Original Tables (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - DH-31: Handicapped Alert- Trip Purpose/Frequency/Distance (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - DH-32: Handicapped Alert- Final Report (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - DH-33: NYC Paratransit System (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - DH-34: Transition Plan (Box 17, Folder 18)
        Transition plan for franchised bus companies
      - DH-35: Brooklyn Study Area (Box 17, Folder 19)
        Analysis of demand in a Brooklyn area where a demonstration project was being considered
      - DH-36: Vehicle Design, Operation (Box 17, Folder 20)
        Specs for the vans being considered
      - DH-37: Eligibility, User Factors (Box 17, Folder 21)
        Consideration of criteria for use of paratransit system
      - DH-38: Paratransit System Requirements; Interrogatories (Box 17, Folder 22)
        Copy of suit filed against the program
      - DH-39: 16 B 2 Analysis (Box 17, Folder 23)
        Analysis of where State funds for vans should be applied.
      - DH-40: Handicapped- 16 B 2 (Box 17, Folder 24)
        Information on the program and associated legislation of the period
      - DH-41: Transportation Strategies (Box 17, Folder 25)
        Culminating analysis. Initial attempts to quantify by small area how many trips would be made by various forms of accessible transportation.
      - DH-41 (2): Handicapped, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
        Keeping up with the issue
  - Reference (DR)
    - DR-1: B' Type Pedestrian Ramp (Box 17, Folder 28)
      Specs for sidewalk corner treatment
    - DR-2: Private Auto Restriction Policy Study (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - DR-3: Exclusive Bus Lanes (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - DR-4: Zip Code Maps (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - DR-5: Brooklyn Bridge Centennial (Box 17, Folder 32)
      Memos on possible sign needs for this event.
    - DR-6: Borough Bus Maps (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - DR-7: Flushing Airport (Box 17, Folder 34)
      Minor related items
    - DR-8: Notes From the Underground (Box 17, Folder 35)
      A few issues of this critic of the NYC transit system for 30 years.
    - DR-9: GWB Bus Station Study (Box 17, Folder 36)
      A Port Authority Study
    - DR-10: Transportation Statistics/Census (Box 17, Folder 37)
      Data Sources
    - DR-11: Parking Concepts (Box 17, Folder 38)
      Minor items
    - DR-12: Brooklyn Bridge, Brooklyn Tower- Esplanade, P & T (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Request for assistance to facilitate construction of esplanade at the Brooklyn Bridge
    - DR-13: Bus Shelter Program (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Memo relating to processing sites for bus shelters
  - Administrative (DA)
    - DA-1: Reproduction Notes (Box 17, Folder 39)
      How to get things done in DOT
    - DA-2: Photographic Services, Silver/Clark (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - DA-3: Map File Inventory (Box 17, Folder 41)
      Keeping track of map
    - DA-4: Warranties, Instructions (Box 17, Folder 42)
      On appliances, Acs, IBMs
    - DA-5: Moving- Administrative (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - DA-6: Computers and Wangs (Box 17, Folder 44)
      Background of the early system
    - DA-7: Correspondence Procedure (Box 17, Folder 45)
      Complexity in large organizations
    - DA-8: Interoffice Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - DA-9: Interoffice Memos, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - DA-10: Payroll Management Systems Material (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - DA-11: Exam Question (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Prepared questions for a civil service exam
    - DA-12: Qualifying/Management Exams (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Applying for permanent status
    - DA-13: Consultants (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Firms seeking work on a ferry study
    - DA-14: Consultant Guidelines (Box 18, Folder 9)